his role will be something like this.
Just assume it's credit manager, ITFC.
So you have to know his role.
And there is also a concept of adding the
Mmh.
Mhm.
business portfolio, credit portfolio,
that is depending if you want it to be,
Yeah.
if you want to match this role,
this business portfolio,
this credit portfolio, that's up to you.
Mhm.
Okay, so you need to know for which user,
what role, what business portfolio,
credit portfolio.
Normally business portfolio,
credit portfolio,
you can be very specific or you can put
it as any, that's up to you. Okay,
so once you know this,
Mhm.
go to access control, go to model access.
Here you have to come to document.
I was just testing at this too,
but I'll just remove it for now.
Let me see and so it's between.
So this is how it is actually for now.
Everybody, it was,
everybody had access to all the.
Uhh...
It was any here,
so that means everybody had access to all,
like everything, so if I just what's...
OK, they can upload,
download the document for,
Yeah, they could upload down any,
and yeah, entity. It was,
and is is is respect of the entity.
I just tested it right now.
I assumed it was, you know,
entity specific, but even entity also,
within an entity,
if you upload a document outside the
entity, if you upload a document,
both are visible here, so...
Once with this being there,
you can sort of add a policy like this.
Click your role, like equal to, select,
you have to find the role. Unfortunately,
there's no way you can search it.
Find the role that you're looking for.
Okay, suppose it is.
A TFC.
It's here. Okay,
you can be specific here or leave it as
any any.
So this just means if the user just has
this role,
they can sort of do whatever action or
you can specifically say this role,
this portfolio,
this credit portfolio can do this action.
It's up to you how granular you want to
Mhm.
be. Okay, and actions are like.
Oh.
cumulative. That means if you put view,
he has the option to search.
Mm.
If you put create,
he has the option to view edit search.
Create.
Okay, delete is the highest option.
Leave document as is and category here.
Okay, okay.
Suppose you want ITFC to only have access
to.
Say, ITFC, you click this.
Okay, okay.
So, can you click OK?
What's going to happen? So in this case,
I would not put any here.
I would put here everything other than
the three. Like if you see one second,
I would do this.
like here and I will leave these three
here.
So what I'm saying is all the user in
this case can access everything except
these three. And for these three,
I'm going to specifically tell which role
has access to which category.
So if I put like this, OK,
in the first line,
just imagine I'm doing it this way.
Are.
You're saying all everybody can access
everything now, ITFC person, whoever,
whatever their role is,
they can access ITFC. So if I click save,
did you get it here?
If you have any doubts,
you can let me know.
And I have to put save and activate, okay?
So...
Once I click save and imagine I'm logging
in as a...
I TFC user.
See over here,
they have access to everything and the
ITFC documents that you put.
Okay,
those other two document category that is
Okay.
ICD and IsDB are not there here.
So this we are doing not on that any
specific road.
Ohh.
We are just doing it for like all the
roles, correct? Like whatever we are.
Yeah, it's for a role,
it's for a role-based business portfolio
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
base, yeah.
Mhm.
And I just remember,
write his e-mail again, it's for,
he wants it for documents and reports.
So first, step by step,
you do it for documents, see if it works,
and then you have to slowly do this for
the reports as well.
But don't do it now because it's a,
I'd suggest first doing it for documents,
Vishal.
see if it works because even I'm doing
some changes on the report access as well.
The.
So honestly,
I don't know how we're going to merge the.
Mm.
No, for OK, yeah, it's better.
Can we at least try to like suggest
brother Ahmed to get tested from your end
once,
because anyhow you are testing out for
different things, no,
for this document perspective.
No, I'm not testing for documents.
I'm testing, not testing exactly.
The thing is in our project,
we have something called this covenants.
Lucy.
And for that,
we have to create covenant reports.
Mm.
Mhm.
And I know that this covenant report is
for ITFC,
and I know that ITFC users only have to
access.
Mhm.
So I know the access also has to be done.
So I just tried it out for ITFC users for
the reports part. And so for now,
Mhm.
just don't do reports.
That's all I'm asking. Just.
We need to do for the documentary that
what you have to do.
Documents. Yeah, just if you want,
that's better for now. And then later on,
Mm.
because I, to be honest,
we are still in a project phase.
I have still yet to give you some
projects, I mean, sorry, tenant to you,
you know, as a part of the project.
So I still have some pending updates to
Mhm.
give you. So.
I'm not sure how I have to still discuss
with Harry,
but how we will merge your tenant,
especially this model changes. Anyway,
Okay, okay.
So, what, what, what we'll do, Kezia?
Okay,
since Ahmed might.
so means I will just check internally
with my access management team, okay,
Mhm.
because anyhow we are just modifying the
rules globally, okay,
Ohh, haha.
so they are the say what we call right
team to means provide an exit or
something like that, okay,
so it's better for first time,
Ohh.
we can just do in front of you,
because anyhow they also need the
guidance, okay.
We will, we will tell him, but better you,
your close eyes should be all through
there,
so can we set up one team session along
Yeah.
with our like internet team and we can do
it right now for that the document part
at least?
No.
A letter.
Yeah, now, yeah, we can do it now, Vishal,
because I know we will see if anyone is
there from the taxes management,
and anyhow,
so can you just wait for some time,
let me check internally,
and based on that,
I'll just communicate over the mail,
and if needed,
we can set up another session and we'll
get them for the dog village.
Go down, it.
OK, OK, hold on, OK.
OK, it's OK, Kezia.
Yeah, yeah, that's fine.
Yeah, OK.
Yeah.
Yeah, thanks, Kezia.
Thanks for the clarification again on
Okay.
this.
No problem.
Thank you. Thank you. Have a good day.
OK, you too. Bye, bye, bye, bye.
Thank you.